A Guide to the Joseph R. Killen Collection, 1720-1985
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Joseph R. Killen Collection, 1720-1985
The Library of Virginia
51897
4.2 cubic feet (10 boxes).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Purchased.
Biographical Information
Joseph Roy Killen was born on 9 November 1941 in Pulaski County, Virginia. He grew up in Indian Head, Maryland, and attended Charles County Community College in Maryland and Mars Hill College in North Carolina. He died in Newport News, Virginia on 13 January 2014.
Scope and Content
Collection, 1720-1985, of Joseph R. Killen (1941-2014) of Newport News, Virginia, containing Virginia county court records, papers of the Collier, Askew, and Edwards families of Halifax and Northampton Counties, North Carolina, and Norfolk, Virginia, papers of William H. Joyner of Suffolk, Virginia, papers of the Deverell and Kimball families of Surry County, Virginia, and miscellaneous records.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Virginia County Court Records.
Series II. Collier-Askew-Edwards Family Papers.
Series III. William H. Joyner Papers.
Series IV. Deverell-Kimball Family Papers.
Series V. Miscellaneous Records.
Contents List
- Series I. Virginia County Court Records., Extent: 4 boxes. (Box 1-3, 10)
  The Virginia county court records include agreements, bonds, deeds, guardian's accounts, inventories and appraisements, powers of attorney, suit papers, and wills from the counties of Albemarle, Caroline, Fluvanna, Gloucester, King and Queen, King George, King William, Nansemond, New Kent, Norfolk City, and York. Most of the records, however, are from Charles City, Isle of Wight, Middlesex, Richmond, and Westmoreland Counties. There are also a few items from the District Court and General Court. The records are arranged by county, and thereunder alphabetically by surname. Dates given are recordation dates.
  - Albemarle County
    - Hopkins, Arthur Sr. to Hopkins, Samuel - Deed, 11 June 1761. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Hopkins, Samuel to Haden, John - Deed, September 1767. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Shields, WIlliam Jr. - Deposition, 9 July 1812. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Caroline County
    - Laughlin, Thomas - Order to Appraise Estate, 15 May 1771. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Charles City County
    - Andrews, Daniel and Binford, Aquilla to Hampton, Samuel - Deed, 10 November 1847. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Armistead, Robert H. to Willis, John M. - Deed, 14 March 1845. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bailey, Judson - Summons, 18 November 1850. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bank of Virginia v. Tyler and Colgin, John, exor. v. Tyler exor. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Barrow, Fielding admor. v. Southall, James B. admor. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bailey, Pierce v. Tyler, William. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Binford, James W. to Pearman, Ellen and Sarah - Deed, 15 October 1863. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Blayton, William B. - Account of Sales, 11 September 1844. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - James G. Bloodgood and Co. v. Stubblefield, John S. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bowry, Thomas v. Bullifant, Absolem. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Brown, Dixon - Will, 18 January 1821. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Carter, Hill to Harrison, William A. - Deed, 5 June 1861. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Carter, John G. v. Ware, Edwin F. and Poindexter, Edward H.. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Chancey, Cary A. to Mouncastle, Beverly - Deed, 18 June 1863. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Christian, Benjamin L. rep. v. Rollison, George W. et. al. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Christian, Edmund v. Fear, John. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Christian, James H. to Manoah Baptist Church Trustees - Deed, 5 October 1848. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Christian, Turner v. Durfey, William admor. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Colley, John to Ladd, Jesse - Deed, 17 February 1831. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Commonwealth v. Blaton, John Henry and Wilson, Josiah. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Commonwealth v. Marable, Major Jr. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Crew Anna et. als. to Crew's Trustee - Deed, 11 March 1844. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Douthat, Eleanor W. - Agreement re: Distribution of Property, 16 June 1849. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Douthat, Robert and Selden, William A. to Taylor, Archibald - Deed, 16 March 1861. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Drinkard, Beverly and Stainback, George W. to Waddil, George C. - Deed, 20 October 1849. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Edloe, Carter admor. v. Minge, John exors. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Eppes, Francis - Deed of Emancipation, 16 April 1846. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Eppes, Peter to Ballard, Francis D. - Deed, December 1796. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Eppes, Robert P. assignee v. Diddep, Dr. John L. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Folkes, Edward to Mohrengar, George - Deed, 16 November 1865. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Galt, William T. v. Apperson, Edmund B.W. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Gary, J.H. to Waddell, Edmund - Power of Attorney, 12 May 1863. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Goddin, Adolphus and Vaiden, Ann E. - Marriage Agreement, 9 November 1863. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Grant, John M. and Jackson, James B. v. Lipscomb, Theoderick B. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Graves, Richard M. assignee v. Holt, John T. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Graves, Richard M. v. Young, Edward D. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Graves, Thomas W. v. Marable, John M. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Graves, William S. v. Apperson, Edmund B.W. and Young, Edward O. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Gregory, Asa with Mann, John, trustee - Account, 20 March 1868. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Harrison, Benjamin et. als. v. Adams, Littleberry. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Harrison, Benjamin to Bradley, Benjamin - Deed, 17 January 1804. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Harrison, Benjamin H. - Will, 20 November 1862. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Harrison, Camilla A.M. v. Haynes, Braxton J. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Harrison, Jane A. to Crane, John R. - Power of Attorney, 29 January 1861. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Harrison, William S. to Ammons, John B. - Deed, 29 October 1849. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Harwood, John T. v. Armistead, John R.. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Harwood, Robert W. v. Holt, John T. and Tyler, William. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Hewitt, Thomas M. asignee v. Christian, James D. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Holcroft, Braxton to Challenner, Burwell - Deed, 30 December 1843. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Holmes, Charles H. to Harwood, Joseph C. - Deed, 20 December 1855. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Hubbard, James, assignee v. Ladd, Lotsey A. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Hubbard, William H. to McManus, George B. - Deed, 4 October 1869. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Jones, Henry L. to Tyler, John Jr. - Deed, 3 November 1845. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Kemp, Oswald S. v. Brown, Albert G. and Graves, William S. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Ladd, James - Will, 7 May 1777. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Lamb, Anthony and John to Dancy, Hardyman - Bond (portion), 11 July 1786. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Lawrence, Nathaniel v. Pemberton, William. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Major, George B. v. Ball, Elijah. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - McCandlish, Col. Robert - Letter, 4 April 1853. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - McElroy, Ellis v. Diddep, Dr. James L. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - McNiece, Williams, and Lowe v. Walker, George. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Minge, Collier H. to Minge, John Sr. and Minge, James - Deed, 20 February 1843. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Minge, Edward - Appraisement, 4 November 1778. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Minge, John v. Creighton, Sally admor. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Minge, John to May, John F. - Trust Deed, 26 April 1843. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Minge, John to Parish, Talbot - Deed, 17 December 1812. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Minge, John to Townes, William W. and Branch, David H. - Trust Deed, 18 April 1845. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Minge, John to Tyler, John - Deed, 17 April 1852. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Nance, Benjamin A. v. Taylor, William H. rep. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Nance, Zachariah F. assignee v. Marable, Major Sr. and Young, Edward D. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - New, Thomas B. to Brown, Robert S. - Deed, 8 May 1861. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Parsons, John L. to Warren, James R. - Deed, 20 August 1863. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Pemberton, William to Rady, Charles P. - Trust Deed, 15 January 1863. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Perry, Daniel v. Boswell, Charles. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Pierce and Henley v. Egmon, John L. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Roper, Edward orphans - Qualification of Guardian, 16 December 1830. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Saunders and Co. v. Walker, Clayton. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Schemerhorne's children v. Schemerhorne. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Scott, James v. Graves, William F. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Selden, John A. to Kay, George and Moon, Charles B. - Deed, 13 May 1851. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Selden, John A. et. als. to Orgain, Martha A. - Deed, 18 November 1843. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Selden, John A. and Saunders, John L. to Harrison, John H. heirs - Deed, 17 May 1860. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Selden, William A. and Willcox, Thomas H. - Agreement, 27 February 1849. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Selden and Miller v. Baker, G.F. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Smith, Silvanus to Babcock, L.E. - Deed, 16 December 1862. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Southall, Elizabeth et. als. to Lacy, Robert E. - Deed, 18 September 1845. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Southall, George W. admor. v. Daingerfield, John. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Spence(?), Sarah - Marriage Consent, 18 September 1790. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Tyler, Hiram W. to Terry, Thomas S. - Deed, 22 September 1871. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Tyler, John H. to Christian, Edmund T. - Deed, 21 July 1849,. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Tyler, Wat H. to Brockenbrough, Austin - Deed, 29 July 1847. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Tyler, William to Charles City Charity School - Bond, 5 June 1843. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Tyler, William v. Royster, Elizabeth. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Vaiden, Leonidas W. v. Graves, William S. and Richard M. - Copy of Record, 1845. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Waddill, Richard E. - Sheriff's Bond, 17 August 1865. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Walker, E.C. v. Graves, Robert W. and Egmon, John L. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Walker, George v. Tyler, William and John. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Walker, William exor. v. Barrow, Fielding admor. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Willcox, Thomas H. to Selden, William A. - Release Deed, 6 March 1863. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Woolfolk, John v. Tyler, William,. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Woolfolk, Thomas v. Crew, Peter - Deed, 18 May 1818. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fluvanna County
    - Appleberry, William A. and Absolam v. Wills, Matthew, shff. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Bernard, Peter to Haden, Anthony - Deed, 4 September 1797. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Haden, John to Haden, William Jr. - Deed, 4 June 1795. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Haden, William v. Bragg, Richard - Survey, 18 October 1811. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Hughes, William Sr. and Forbes, John to Brookes, William - Appeal Bond, 25 January 1813. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Lee, Kendall to James, John - Bond to Stay Execution, 20 March 1809. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Lee, Kendall to Lewis, Warner and Lee, George K. - Deed of Trust, 26 May 1809. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Lee, Kendall to William R. Richards and Co. - Bond to Stay Execution, 21 March 1809. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - May, John and Wiliam - Guardian's Accounts, 1795, 1797. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Payne, William and Thompson, Roger - Executors Bond, 6 November 1797. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Scott, John - Administrator's Bond, 7 May 1798. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Scott, Joseph - Inventory and Appraisement, 4 June 1798. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Willis, Matthew and Johnson, John to Allen, Richard exors. - Forthcoming Bond, 26 July 1813. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Wills, Matthew et. als. v. Monroe, James for Shelton, Samuel. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gloucester County
    - Brooking, Mary Jane to Deadman, Alexander - Deed, 3 June 1907. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Dedmon, Pendleton to Harris, Frank - Deed, 4 June 1907. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Fosque, John T. - Merchant License Application, 4 May 1891. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Isle of Wight County
    - Backhurst, John B.S. - Will, 5 February 1816. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Bowins, George - Will, 6 May 1816. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Bracy, Nancy - Will, 15 October 1816. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Bradshaw, Jonas - Will, 5 February 1816. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Carson, Richard - Appraisement, 5 February 1816. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Chapman, Samuel - Inventory and Appraisement, 1 January 1816. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Cocke, Richard - Will, 5 February 1816. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Coffield, William - Account of Sales, 6 May 1816. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Crocker, Milner - Inventory and Appraisement, 3 June 1816. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Darden, Benjamin - Inventory and Appraisement, 10 November 1815. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Fulgham, Lemuel - Will, 6 May 1816. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Gay, William - Will, 5 February 1816. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Gray, Josiah - Account Current, 7 October 1816. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Gray, Josiah - Account of Sales, 7 October 1816. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Gray, Martha - Account Current, 7 October 1816. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Gray, Martha - Account of Sales, 7 October 1816. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Groce, Charles - Account Current, 4 March 1816. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Herring, Natt - Will, 1 January 1816. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Herring, Natt - Will, 5 August 1816. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Herring, Patsey - Will, 6 May 1816. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Holladay, Samuel - Account Current, 4 March 1816. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Jenkins, William - Account Current, 6 May 1816. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Johnson, Amos - Will, 6 May 1816. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Johnson, Joseph - Will, 1 January 1816. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Joyner, John - Inventory and Appraisement, 6 May 1816. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Meador, Banister - Will, 1 July 1816. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Mountfortt, Wade - Will, 5 February 1816. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Mountfortt, Wade - Account of Sales, 3 June 1816. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Roberts, William et. als. v. Roberts, Willis. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Robertson, Jonathan - Order to Appraise Estate, 1815. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Shivers, George - Will, 1 January 1816. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Waterfield, Jacob - Will, 4 November 1816. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Whitly, William - Will, 30 December 1813. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Wills, Mills - Inventory and Appraisement, 4 March 1816. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Wrench, John - Inventory and Appraisement, 3 June 1816. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - King and Queen County
    - Carlton, John A. v. Dyke, John B. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Clarkson, John H. v. Noel, Robert S. admx. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Montague, Edgar B. v. Bray, Joel E. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Poll - Senate of Virginia, 12 October 1865. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Southall, George W. admx. v. Dangerfield, Augustine B. admor. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Tolley, John A. v. Edwards, A. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - King George County
    - Anderson, William v. Stuart, John G. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Ashton, Mary - Relinquishment of Dower, 23 January 1794. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Beck, James assignee to Page, William B. - Forthcoming Bond, 4 April 1820 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Commonwealth v. Reynolds, Samuel. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Foot, Malachi v. Bernard, William. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Grayson, Richard exor. v. Grayson, Robert O. admor. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Hooe and Rogers to Grymes, George N. - Forthcoming Bond, 26 April 1820. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Hopkins, Bazil assignee v. Davis, Addison. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Hopkins, Bazil assignee v. Edwards, John. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Hopkins, Bazil assignee v. Johnson, George B. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Jaffray, James assignee to Stuart, John G. - Forthcoming Bond, 25 April 1820. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Knox, William A. and John S. assignees v. Stuart, William G. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Ladd and Co. v. Dade, Langhorne, admor. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Owens, Reuben to Fitzhugh, Henry - Forthcoming Bond, 1 May 1820. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Pollard, Marcy admx. to Roach, James et. als. - Forthcoming Bond, 30 May 1820. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Price, Thornton et. als. v. Price, Elizabeth et. als. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Richards, Mark assignee to Grymes, George N. - Forthcoming Bond, 26 April 1820. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Sedwick, James C. v. Grymes, George N. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Starke, William J. v. Butcher, Jonathan. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Stewart, William assignee to Fitzhugh, Henry et. als. - Forthcoming Bond, 1 May 1820. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - King William County
    - Spencer, Sally - Relinquishment of Dower, 10 December 1830. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Middlesex County
    - Andrews, Thomas P. - Letter, 6 April 1829. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Batchelder, John - Inventory and Appraisement, 7 March 1720. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Batchelder, Sarah - Inventory and Appraisement, 6 June 1721. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Berkeley, Lewis - Inventory and Appraisement, 4 February 1745. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Blakey, Mary - Inventory and Appraisement, 6 May 1746. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Braxton, Thomas C. to Braxton, Carter M. - Deed of Mortgage, 22 January 1821. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Chew, John to Braxton, Carter M. - Receipt, 25 February 1828. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Chilton, Mary - Inventory and Appraisement, 5 June 1744. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Chowning, John Jr. - Coroner's Commission, 6 January 1813. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Chowning, John Jr. - Coronor's Bond, 25 January 1813. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Churchill, Armistead - Inventory and Appraisement, 9 August 1763. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Churchill, Thomas to Robinson, Peter - Deed, 22 June 1807. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Daniel, Garret - Inventory and Appraisement, 2 July 1745. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Grymes, Philip Ludwell - Will, 24 June 1805. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Lee, Charles - Inventory and Appraisement (portion), 4 April 1721. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Lee, John to Parron, William - Deed, 28 September 1812. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Lewis, Elizabeth - Inventory and Appraisement, 1768. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Marshall, John - Inventory and Appraisement, 2 September 1740. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Mickelburrough, Henry - Inventory and Appraisement, 27 July 1784. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Owen, John to Jones, Catesby, trustee - Deed, 28 August 1826. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Pace, John - Order to Appraise Estate, 7 March 1720. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Robinson, John - Will, 21 February 1785. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Robinson, Robert to Robinson, John - Power of Attorney, 22 July 1811. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Shelton, Thomas - Inventory and Appraisement, 5 July 1743. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Steptoe, James R. - Sheriff's Bond, 27 March 1826. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Stevens, James W. - Escheator Bond, 17 September 1824. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Stiff, James - Order to Appraise Estate, 23 June 1791. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Thurston, John - Estate Settlement, 26 April 1773. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Tuggle, Henry - Settlement of Estate, 22 April 1771. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Walker, John - Inventory and Appraisement, 6 May 1746. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Warwick, Mary - Order to Appraise Estate, 1720. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Wormeley, Ralph Jr. and Wormeley, Ralph - Agreement, 6 June 1805. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Yates, Bartholomew - Division of Slaves, 6 February 1770. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Yates, Bartholomew - Inventory and Appraisement, 5 June 1771. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified Inventory. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Nansemond County
    - Daughtrey, Jacob K. to Daughtrey, Jacob K.P. - Deed, 15 July 1868. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Daughtrey, L.J. and Jennie J. - Receipts, 24 and 26 February 1937. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Holland, E.E. - Notary Public Commission, 21 January 1886. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Holy Neck District No. 2 School Board to J.K.P. Daughtrey - Deed, 8 March 1915. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - New Kent County
    - Blassingham, William T. to Tyree, Alonzo - Deed, 14 December 1865. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Carter, Judith to Crump, David S.M. - Deed, 5 January 1836. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Crump, David S.M. - Survey, June 1833. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Davis, Thomas to Pollard, Elisha and Crump, Edmund P.C. - Deed, 9 February 1832. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Douglas, William R.C. to Munford, Robert H. - Deed, 9 February 1837. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Hilliard, Robert to Crump, David S.M. - Deed, 10 July 1834. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Howle, Christopher and Clarke, Freeman to Crump, David S.M. - Deed, 14 August 1834. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Leake, T.C. to Barham, Thomas trustee - Deed, 15 November 1866. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Pearce, Lockey M. to Crump, David S.M. - Deed, 11 June 1835. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Sherman, William M. to Crump, David S.M. - Deed, 10 July 1834. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Tyree, Abner to Jones, Chesley - Deed, 11 August 1835. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Wade, Seaton to Crump, David S.M. - Deed, 8 May 1834. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Norfolk City
    - The Berkeley Citizens' Mutual Building and Loan to Taylor, Lillie R. - Release Deed, 21 December 1931. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Richmond County
    - Alderson, Jeremiah to Fox, Isaac - Apprenticeship Indenture, 2 April 1759. (Box 2, Folder 7)